[
    {
        "question":" What is the maximum length of a Python identifier?",
        "option1":"32 ",
        "option2":" 16 ",
        "option3":"128",
        "option4":" no fixed length",
        "answer":"no fixed length"
    },
    {
        "question":" What will be the output of the following code snippet? print(2*3 + (5 + 6)*(1 + 1))",
        "option1":"129 ",
        "option2":"8 ",
        "option3":"121",
        "option4":"none of the above",
        "answer":"129 "
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following statements are used in Exception Handling in Python?",
        "option1":" try",
        "option2":"finally ",
        "option3":" except",
        "option4":"all of the above",
        "answer":"all of the above "
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is the proper syntax to check if a particular element is present in a list? ",
        "option1":" if ele in  list",
        "option2":"if not ele not in list",
        "option3":"Both A and B ",
        "option4":"none of the above",
        "answer":"Both A and B "
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following functions converts date to corresponding time in Python?",
        "option1":"strptime()",
        "option2":"strftime()",
        "option3":"Both A and B ",
        "option4":"none of the above",
        "answer":"strptime() "
    },
    {
        "question":"What will be the output of the following code snippet?- from math import *;a = 2.19;b = 3.999999; c = -3.30;print(int(a), floor(b), ceil(c), fabs(c)) ;",
        "option1":"2 3 -3 3.3 ",
        "option2":"3 4 -3 3",
        "option3":"2 3 -3 3",
        "option4":"2 3 -3 -3.3 ",
        "answer":"2 3 -3 3.3"
    },
    {
        "question":"What will be the result of the following expression in Python “2 * 3 + 5 * 2”?",
        "option1":"65536",
        "option2":" 33",
        "option3":"169",
        "option4":"none of the above",
        "answer":" 33"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following are valid string manipulation functions in Python? ",
        "option1":"count()",
        "option2":"upper() ",
        "option3":"strip()",
        "option4":"all of the above",
        "answer":"all of the above "
    },
    {
        "question":"What will be the output of the following code snippet? a = [1, 2, 3, 4]; b = [3, 4, 5, 6];c = [x for x in a if x not in b];print(c) ",
        "option1":" [1,2]",
        "option2":"[5,6]",
        "option3":"[1,2,5,6]",
        "option4":"[3,4] ",
        "answer":"[1,2]"
    },
    {
        "question":"As what datatype are the *kwargs stored, when passed into a function?",
        "option1":"lists",
        "option2":"dictionary",
        "option3":"tuples ",
        "option4":"none of the above",
        "answer":"dictionary"
    }
]